Bradley Hill 
bhill0052@yahoo.com



1) Step 1: Gather data(thanks Wikipedia)
     Penny diameter: 19.05 mm
     Golden Gate Bridge length:  2737.4 m
                                         width:   24.7 m

     Step 2:  Convert to same units
     19.05  * .01 = .1905 m

      Step 3: Divide length of the bridge by the diameter of a penny
      2737.4 / .1905 = 14369 pennies

      Step 4: Divide width of the bridge by the diameter of a a penny
      24.7 / .1905 = 129 pennies 

      Step 5: Multiply the answers from steps 3 and 4
      14369 * 129 = 1853601 pennies

      Answer:
      1,853,601 pennies could fit on the Golden Gate Bridge without any of them overlapping.

      Notes:
      I chose to use metric units for this problem since it would make for easier conversions.  Also I rounded down to the nearest whole penny since there could be no overlap(if you allowed the pennies to hang off the edges of the bridge it would have been 1,868,100 pennies).



2)  16:9  (with width fixed at 12 pixel increments)

     Answer: 
     192 x 108, 960 x 540, 1920 x 1080

      Notes: 
      I just chose to go simply with a small size that fit the limitations then scale that by 5 times and 10 times(respectively).



3)  Since there are 64 spaces on a chess board it would take a MINIMUM of 64 moves (63 if you count the starting position).  My program however was only able to do it in 74 moves (84 in the example used for my graph, knightgraph.jpg).

      Notes:
      When I started working on this problem I thought it would be best to try to solve it on paper first, then make my algorithm from that solution.  While I was able to come close to solving it, my algorithm was more intuitive than systematic.  So I decided to try to solve it instead by making that "intuition" into a program and let it solve the problem.  The program I ended up with basically tries to move to an unvisited space when possible, and towards one when there isn't one within the current movement range.  After later discussing the problem with a friend, I realized that a recursive algorithm would have worked better, though I have to admit my skills at developing recursive algorithms are a bit rusty. (knight.cpp and knight.exe)



4)  For this one I decided to make a "Fire" themed collage out of the things that I'm most passionate about in my own life: games, Japanese language and culture, and, of course, IGN.  I used game screen shots containing fiery images from that I found on IGN, and arranged them in the pattern of the Japanese kanji "火" (meaning "fire").

While I can come up with some pretty creative ideas, I'm no artist so I stuck with MS Paint. (fire.jpg)